Set Thu Han

Myanmar | +95-9962874015 | setthuhan.Dev@outlook.com

Dear Hiring Team,

I hope your day has been going well so far! My name is Set Thu Han and I am a former Unity game developer with 3 years of experience. As a passion driven employee, I know my versatile skills and qualifications will make me a valuable asset to the team.

As you will find on my resume, I have had a variety of experiences with my passionate role in game development, from my time as Unity game developer to senior game developer. Right now, I am looking to make the next step in my career by leveraging my skills and knowledge in game development and gaming industry.

As a prospective employee, I immediately can bring the following qualities to the team:

- 1. Quick prototypes: When I was a Unity game developer, I was assigned to develop F2P game prototypes based on clients' descriptions within 10 days. In these given days, I had to make required game effects and animations if they are not available on Unity asset store. That's why I had the experiences in not only developing desired game mechanics and gameplays but also making game effects in a given time, and gained trust by the clients as my assigned prototype enlisted on top 10 trending hit list at that time.
- 2. Themes and concepts: In my recent position as senior game developer, I was involved to develop embedded web games based on raw contents, and I had to make every decision on designs and guidance on themes to a junior graphic designer while controlling qualities of embedded game graphics and its performance, and had to sketch concepts from start to finish, targeting for kids who age around $3 \sim 5$. The impacts from this position gave me full multitasking, quick decisions and quality control over performance of the games.

While my resume provides a quick summary of my experiences, I hope to have the opportunity to share how I can bring value to your company's needs. Thank you for your time, I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely, Set

Set Thu Han

<u>setthuhan.Dev@outlook.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/set-thu-han</u> | <u>github.io/portfolio</u> Yangon, Myanmar | +95-9962874015

WORK EXPERIENCES

DKMads Co., Ltd (Digital Advertising)

Senior Game Developer

Feb 2023 - April 2024

- Developed educational, casual, and turn-based optimized In-App Web games using Unity WebGL and utilized Flutter Web-View content.
- Worked closely with graphic designer to create game concept's and UI/UX designs from initial to final state, especially for kids who age around $3 \sim 5$.
- Developed whole multiplayer Unity WebGL game using Socket.io in NodeJs by integrating back and forth to main application to invite or challenge in-app and in-game active users.

Myanmar51 Studio (Animations & CG Co., Ltd)

Unity Game Developer & QC

Nov 2020 - Nov 2022

- Replaced Unity Ads SDK with another one called LionSDK by Applovin and upgraded old SDK with new updated one, and fixed bugs throughout upgrading process.
- Made quick game prototypes within 10 days per one prototype with quality does matter.
- Guided interns and new juniors how to get the qualities, effects by using Unity Shaders, and post-process the game what the clients want.
- Published two or more in-house F2P games to PlayStore and AppStore, integrated with AppLovin monetizing SDK.
- Involved in adding new features such as bingo systems, localizations, UI effects, and random gift systems for Tiny Park (Sanrio Characters' 10 mini games) and fixing bugs of other developers'.
- Made closest AAA qualitied rendered videos from initial to final state based on clients' scripts by utilizing full potentials of Unity HDRP with timelines and sequences.
- Researched and made custom Unity Shaders and VFX effects based on requirements.

RESEARCH PROJECTS

- Stylized Custom Color-Ripple-Dissolve effects by utilizing Unity ShaderGraph
- Stylized Custom Anime Water effect by utilizing Unity ShaderGraph
- Dynamic full-screen volumetric fog by utilizing Unity ShaderGraph and custom HLSL

EDUCATION

Technological University (Hmawbi) | 2013 - 2019

Bachelor of Engineering in Mechatronics

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Computer: C#, Unity (Built-In/URP/HDRP), Blender 3D (Modeling, Animations),

Python (Machine Learning, Data Analysis, Data Visualization), NodeJs (SocketIO),

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Familiarities: AWS, Firebase, GCP, IBM Cloud, Linux

Language: Upper B2 - English | Native - Myanmar | N5 - Japanese

Interests: Career development, learning new programming language, open world gaming

CERTIFICATIONS

• Design Patterns for Game Programming – Udemy

July 19, 2021

• Applied Data Science Specialization - Coursera Course Certificates

Aug 29, 2020

• IBM AI Engineering Specialization - Coursera Course Certificates

Oct 03, 2020